<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollView</string>
    <string name="textview">>Sabrina Carpenter, born on May 11, 1999, in Quaker town, Pennsylvania, is a multifaceted American singer, songwriter, and actress. She began her entertainment career at a young age, gaining prominence through her role as Maya Hart on Disney Channel\'s "Girl Meets World" (2014–2017).
SABRINA CARPENTER
Music Career:
Carpenter\'s musical journey commenced with her debut single "Can't Blame a Girl for Trying" in 2014, followed by her first studio album, "Eyes Wide Open," in 2015. She has since released several albums, including "Evolution" (2016), "Singular: Act I" (2018), "Singular: Act II" (2019), and "Emails I Can't Send" (2022). Her latest album, "Short n' Sweet," released in August 2024, debuted atop the Billboard 200 and features chart-topping singles like "Espresso" and "Please Please Please."
WIKIPEDIA
Acting Endeavors
Beyond her Disney Channel success, Carpenter has showcased her acting versatility in various films and television projects. Notable appearances include "Law and Order: Special Victims Unit," "The Hate U Give" (2018), "The Short History of the Long Road" (2019), and Netflix productions such as "Tall Girl" (2019) and its sequel, "Tall Girl 2" (2022). She also starred in and executive-produced the Netflix dance comedy "Work It" (2020).
WIKIPEDIA
Recent Highlights:
Music Video Cameo: In June 2024, Carpenter's boyfriend, actor Barry Keoghan, made a surprise appearance in her music video for the single "Please Please Please," which features a Bonnie and Clyde-inspired storyline.
THE SUN
Award Recognition: In September 2024, she won a Video Music Award for Song of the Year for her hit "Espresso," expressing heartfelt gratitude towards her fans and family during her acceptance speech.
NEWS.COM.AU
Fashion Spotlight: Carpenter garnered media attention for her fashion choices, notably wearing a sixties-inspired see-through lace bridal dress at a VMAs after-party in September 2024.
NEWS.COM.AU
Personal Life:
Carpenter maintains a relatively private personal life. She has been linked romantically to actor Barry Keoghan, with the couple making public appearances together, including at the Met Gala in May 2024.
BILD
Sabrina Carpenter continues to evolve as a prominent figure in the entertainment industry, seamlessly blending her talents in music and acting while captivating audiences worldwide.</string>

</resources>